<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>System requirements for PrestaShop 1.7</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>.h-version-titles th:not(:first-child) { text-align: center; } .support-yes, .example-yes { background-color: #8ce48c; text-align: center; } .support-no, .example-no { background-color: #e89b9b; } .example-yes, .example-no { display: inline-block; width: 1.1rem; height: 1.1rem; margin-bottom: -2px; }  System requirements for PrestaShop 1.7 PrestaShop needs the following server configuration in order to run:
 System: Unix, Linux or Windows. Web server: Apache Web Server 2.2 or any later version. PHP: We recommend PHP 7.1 or later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing a local environment</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/localhost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/localhost/</guid>
      <description>Installing PrestaShop for development Now that you intend to develop for PrestaShop, you are better off keeping all your development work on your machine. The main advantage is that it makes it possible for you to entirely bypass the process of uploading your file on your online server in order to test it. Another advantage is that a local test environment enables you to test code without the risk of breaking your production store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Apache Http</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/httpd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/httpd/</guid>
      <description>Configure Apache Httpd The following file is provided as an example configuration for your Apache server. It may be incomplete, and remember you must adapt it for your own server&amp;rsquo;s needs!
 In Apache 2.4, Order Allow,Deny has been replaced by Require all granted. We assume you are using Apache Http 2.4 or higher.
 With mod_php/PHP-CGI &amp;lt;VirtualHost *:80&amp;gt; # or 443 for SSL support ServerName example.com DocumentRoot /path/to/prestashop # SSLEngine on # SSLCertificateFile /etc/apache2/ssl/example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Nginx</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/nginx/</guid>
      <description>Configure Nginx The following file is provided as an example configuration for your Nginx server. It may be incomplete, and remember you must adapt it for your own server&amp;rsquo;s needs!
server { # Ipv4  listen 80; # IPv6  # listen [::]:80;  # SSL Ipv4 &amp;amp; v6  # listen 443 ssl http2;  # listen [::]:443 ssl;  # Your SSL Certificates, don&amp;#39;t forget to take a look at Certbot (https://certbot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuring PrestaShop By default, PrestaShop is configured to provide a secure and stable environment to both the shop administrator and the customers.
As a developer, there are several changes that you could and should bring to the default installation in order to help you code better, spot bugs faster, and generally make a great PrestaShop product.
Disabling the cache and forcing Smarty compilation When your development has an impact on the front office, whether you are building a theme or simply a module which displays information to the customer, you should force the template file compilation and disable the cache, so as to always see the result of your changes directly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
