<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>System requirements for PrestaShop 1.7</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>System requirements for PrestaShop 1.7PrestaShop needs the following server configuration in order to run:&#xA;System: Unix, Linux or Windows. Web server: Apache Web Server 2.2 or any later version. PHP: We recommend PHP 7.1 or later. See the compatibility chart below for more details. MySQL: 5.6 minimum, a recent version is recommended. Server RAM: The more the merrier. We recommend setting the memory allocation per script (memory_limit) to a minimum of 256M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing a local environment</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/localhost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/localhost/</guid>
      <description>Installing PrestaShop for developmentNow that you intend to develop for PrestaShop, you are better off keeping all your development work on your machine. The main advantage is that it makes it possible for you to entirely bypass the process of uploading your file on your online server in order to test it. Another advantage is that a local test environment enables you to test code without the risk of breaking your production store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing PrestaShop from CLI</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/install-from-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/install-from-cli/</guid>
      <description>Installing PrestaShop from CLISince version 1.5.4, PrestaShop has a command-line installer.&#xA;This special installer makes it possible to install PrestaShop without the need to use a web browser: simply put the content of the zip archive on your web server or pull code from an official PrestaShop repository, and you can install PrestaShop through your command-line interface (CLI).&#xA;If deploying from sources (PrestaShop repository), you must first install Composer dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Apache Http</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/httpd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/httpd/</guid>
      <description>Configure Apache HttpdThe following file is provided as an example configuration for your Apache server. It may be incomplete, and remember you must adapt it for your own server&amp;rsquo;s needs!&#xA;In Apache 2.4, Order Allow,Deny has been replaced by Require all granted. We assume you are using Apache Http 2.4 or higher.&#xA;With mod_php/PHP-CGI&amp;lt;VirtualHost *:80&amp;gt; # or 443 for SSL support ServerName example.com DocumentRoot /path/to/prestashop # SSLEngine on # SSLCertificateFile /etc/apache2/ssl/example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Nginx</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/nginx/</guid>
      <description>Configure NginxThe following file is provided as an example configuration for your Nginx server. It may be incomplete, and remember you must adapt it for your own server&amp;rsquo;s needs!&#xA;Once you are comfortable with your setup make sure to review our guide on how to optimize your Nginx configuration to better suit your requirements.&#xA;server { # IPv4. listen 80; listen 443 ssl http2; # IPv6. # listen [::]:80; # listen [::]:443 ssl http2; # [EDIT] Your domain name(s) go here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/installation/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuring PrestaShopBy default, PrestaShop is configured to provide a secure and stable environment to both the shop administrator and the customers.&#xA;As a developer, there are several changes that you could and should bring to the default installation in order to help you code better, spot bugs faster, and generally make a great PrestaShop product.&#xA;Disabling the cache and forcing Smarty compilationWhen your development has an impact on the front office, whether you are building a theme or simply a module which displays information to the customer, you should force the template file compilation and disable the cache, so as to always see the result of your changes directly.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
