<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PrestaShop UI Kit on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PrestaShop UI Kit on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UI Kit</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/uikit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/uikit/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the PrestaShop UIKit?The UIKit is a project extending Bootstrap 4 in order to provide some components with PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s colors. You can see every component on this page.&#xA;How do we use the UIKit?We use it by adding it into our npm dependency, and then you&amp;rsquo;ve multiple possibilities to use it.&#xA;You can import dist files, it means that you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to use our variables outside of the UIKit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS variables reference</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/variables-reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/variables-reference/</guid>
      <description>CSS variables referenceDiscover a summary of the main CSS variables available through the PrestaShop UI Kit.&#xA;See exposed CSS variables ColorsThese variables should be used when you want to apply a color on the BO.&#xA;Main Variable name Used for (non-exhaustive list) Primary --cdk-primary-900 ... --cdk-primary-800 Header background / Primary button background --cdk-primary-700 Buttons states --cdk-primary-600 UI elements / On login page --cdk-primary-500 Some icons / Buttons states --cdk-primary-400 Borders color --cdk-primary-300 Nav bar / Buttons states / Tables --cdk-primary-200 Disabled form elements / Tables --cdk-primary-100 Tables Red --cdk-red-700 Alert, Destructive, Danger elements --cdk-red-500 --cdk-red-300 --cdk-red-100 --cdk-red-50 Purple --cdk-purple-700 New branding color --cdk-purple-500 --cdk-purple-50 Blue --cdk-blue-700 UI / States, Infos elements --cdk-blue-500 --cdk-blue-300 --cdk-blue-100 --cdk-blue-50 Ocean blue --cdk-ocean-blue-700 New branding color --cdk-ocean-blue-500 --cdk-ocean-blue-50 Yellow --cdk-yellow-500 Warning elements --cdk-yellow-300 --cdk-yellow-100 --cdk-yellow-50 Amber --cdk-amber-500 New branding color --cdk-amber-100 Green --cdk-green-500 Success elements --cdk-green-300 --cdk-green-100 --cdk-green-50 Black --cdk-black .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use it?</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/how-to-use-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/how-to-use-it/</guid>
      <description>How to use a new set of CSS variables?To maintain consistency across the PrestaShop back office, CSS variables have been introduced in _root.scss. This guide explains how to use them.&#xA;Using CSS variables in PrestaShop 9.0+In PrestaShop v9 and later, we use the CSS variables introduced in _root.scss for consistent styling in the back office.&#xA;Usage Example/* CSS: Apply dark background on a block */ .my-block { background-color: var(--cdk-primary-800); } /* SCSS: Apply dark background on a block */ .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS variables</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/css-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/9/development/ui-kit/css-variables/</guid>
      <description>CSS variables in PrestaShop UI KitPrestaShop UI Kit uses CSS variables for design harmonization in the back office.&#xA;Why use CSS variables?CSS variables provide several advantages in large-scale projects like PrestaShop:&#xA;1. Avoiding naming conflictsIn projects with multiple themes or libraries, variable names can overlap. Using prefixes like cdk- (Core Design Kit) ensures that variables are unique and do not override variables from other parts of the project or third-party libraries.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
