<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hooks on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/hooks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hooks on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/hooks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>List of hooks</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/hooks/list-of-hooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/hooks/list-of-hooks/</guid>
      <description>List of hooks in PrestaShop 1.7 Update notes A couple of hooks were modified between 1.7.0.x and 1.7.1.x.
 actionDeleteProductInCartAfter has been divided into two hooks:  actionObjectProductInCartDeleteBefore. actionObjectProductInCartDeleteAfter.   displayProductButtons has been renamed into displayProductAdditionalInfo.
Don’t worry, we kept an alias :)  Full list Search tip: Some hooks are generated dynamically, so their names are documented in a generic way.
For example, actionAdminCustomersFormModifier is documented as action&amp;lt;AdminControllerClassName&amp;gt;FormModifier, so you won&amp;rsquo;t find it if you search for the exact name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use hooks on modern pages</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/hooks/use-hooks-on-modern-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/hooks/use-hooks-on-modern-pages/</guid>
      <description>Use hooks on modern pages You know you can already customize your PrestaShop store thanks to many hooks: the good news is that you can still use hooks like you did in the earlier versions of PrestaShop in modern pages.
Starting from PrestaShop 1.7.3, you can access the modern Services Container into your modules and so on access powerful and customizable features available in Symfony:
 Twig, the most popular templating engine; Swiftmailer, a feature-rich mailer; Doctrine ORM and Doctrine DBAL to manage your database; Filesystem and Finder libraries to manage all filesystem operations; Monolog for every logging operations; Serializer library for whom who need to manipulate Json and Xml formats&amp;hellip;  Of course, you also have access to every service used by the Core of PrestaShop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
