<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Module translation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/creation/module-translation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Module translation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/creation/module-translation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New translation system</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/creation/module-translation/new-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/creation/module-translation/new-system/</guid>
      <description>New module translation system  The new module translation system is based on the new system introduced in PrestaShop 1.7 for the Core and Native modules. It aims to harmonize translation systems throughout PrestaShop while providing backwards compatibility.
This feature is only available for PrestaShop 1.7.6 and later. If you need to support older versions, see the Classic translation system. Vocabulary  Wording – A string that you may want to translate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic translation system</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/creation/module-translation/classic-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/creation/module-translation/classic-system/</guid>
      <description>Classic module translation system The classic translation system is a heritage from previous versions of PrestaShop and provides retrocompatibility with PrestaShop 1.6.
Do you need this?
 If you plan on supporting only versions 1.7.6 and up, consider using the New translation system. Modern (symfony-based) modules and native modules only support the new system.   How it works This system works in two steps.
1. Translation functions are used to display your module&amp;rsquo;s wordings in another language PrestaShop provides functions that allow PHP files and Smarty templates to display translated wordings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparison between Classic translation system and New translation system</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/creation/module-translation/comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/creation/module-translation/comparison/</guid>
      <description>Comparison between Classic and New translation systems Module developers might be confused by both the Classic and New translation systems coexisting together. This page aims to help you choose the best one for your module.
What translation system is best for my module? The best translation system for your module depends on two factors:
 The minimum version of PrestaShop you intend to support:
If you target 1.7.5 or earlier, you need to use the Classic system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
