<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Extension concepts on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Extension concepts on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Widgets</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/widgets/</guid>
      <description>Widgets Widget is an advanced concept introduced on PrestaShop 1.7, extending hooks feature.
Limitation of hooks In their basic use, a display hook will be shown at a specific place in the template. If a module wants to display the same additional content on several places, whatever the merchant chose, it still has to register and implement all the possible hooks.
With widgets, module developers can display content everywhere the module is asked to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overrides</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/overrides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/overrides/</guid>
      <description>Overrides Overriding is a way to &amp;ldquo;override&amp;rdquo; class files and controller files. PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s ingenious class auto-loading function makes the &amp;ldquo;switch&amp;rdquo; to other files fairly simple. Thanks to PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s fully object-oriented code, you can rely on object inheritance to modify and add new behaviors, using the properties and methods of the various existing classes.
Important note There are limitations and risks of using overrides. Keep them for your own shop. Overrides in PrestaShop are exclusive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External dependencies &amp; autoload with Composer</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/composer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/composer/</guid>
      <description>Composer Composer is a tool known in the PHP ecosystem to manage the dependencies of a project. It has been originally added in PrestaShop 1.7 to handle the inclusion of the Symfony framework and the native modules. As composer is compatible with PHP 5.3, it can be used in a module even compatible with previous major versions of PrestaShop.
From a single configuration file, a module will benefit of these features:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symfony extension concepts</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/symfony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/symfony/</guid>
      <description>Symfony extension concepts PrestaShop modules acts as Symfony bundles, extension points are added continuously in each minor version:
   Version Symfony features     1.7.3 Twig templates and Services   1.7.4 Configuration Forms and Console commands   1.7.5 Modern controllers and Security   1.7.6 Doctrine ORM and Entity forms   1.7.7 Controllers as services    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commands</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/commands/</guid>
      <description>Commands  Since version 1.7 of PrestaShop, everyone have access to the PrestaShop console using the following instruction in a terminal:
./bin/console
Since v1.7.5, you can add and provide your own commands into the PrestaShop console using modules.
If you load and use PrestaShop Core legacy classes such as an ObjectModel within a Command context, you might run into issues. This is a known limitation of the Commands. Removing this limitation is being explored for future PS versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pdf Files</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/pdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/pdf/</guid>
      <description>Pdf Files One of the interaction with the Customers involve sending mails, including pdf files.
For example, for every order you do on a Shop as a Customer we expect to receive an Invoice.
Working on what make a shop an unique experience, as a Developer you will be asked to customize every PDF files that PrestaShop can produce.
You can alter the rendering using the provided data or push the PDF Rendering to its best, introducing your very own information that will made your PDF files amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multistore</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/multistore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/concepts/multistore/</guid>
      <description>Specifics of multistore module development Usage of configuration variables As indicated in the Configuration section, some of the methods from the Configuration object have three optional parameters, which make it possible to target any other existing store on the current PrestaShop installation: id_shop, id_shop_group and id_lang.
While these parameters can prove useful when having to handle multiple specific and known stores from one of the presented Configuration method, they are not recommended for general usage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
