<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internationalization on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/internationalization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internationalization on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/internationalization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Localization packs</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/internationalization/localization-packs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/internationalization/localization-packs/</guid>
      <description>Localization packs Wordings in the software are exported into Crowdin, a translation platform. This allows contributors to translate these into all supported languages.
Each night, a cron job fetches translations from Crowdin, updates the PrestaShop/TranslationFiles repository with new updates, and deploys translations to domain i18n.prestashop.com.
i18n.prestashop.com is a domain hosted by PrestaShop company to store all supported Languages Localization Packages. This is the domain where localization packs are downloaded when you use the &amp;ldquo;Download a Language Pack&amp;rdquo; feature in Back Office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Right-To-Left languages</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/internationalization/rtl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/internationalization/rtl/</guid>
      <description>Right-to-Left languages PrestaShop supports Right-to-Left (RTL) languages natively, both in the Back Office and the Front Office. It can automatically transform themes to make them compatible with RTL languages.
Any Front Office theme can be transformed automatically by PrestaShop. Read &amp;ldquo;RTL support&amp;rdquo; in the Themes section to learn more about this system.
Back Office support The Back Office uses the same &amp;ldquo;theme-flipping&amp;rdquo; system as the Front Office feature. While for Front Office themes the transformation procedure must be triggered manually, in the BO this is performed automatically whenever an RTL language is activated on the shop, either by installing an RTL language or by setting up a language as RTL via edit in the BO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
