<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How to update PrestaShop on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How to update PrestaShop on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post-restore checklist</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/post-restore-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/post-restore-checklist/</guid>
      <description> Post-restore checklistBelow is a list of actions that should be done following a PrestaShop restore.&#xA;Main steps Disable the maintenance mode in General settings &amp;gt; Maintenance. Troubleshooting If you can&amp;rsquo;t access your back office, try emptying the cache. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-update checklist</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/post-update-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/post-update-checklist/</guid>
      <description>Post-update checklistBelow is a list of actions that should be done following a PrestaShop update.&#xA;Main stepsThe following steps will be executed during the upgrade:&#xA;Refresh the page. You’ll need to sign in to your back office again. Re-enable and check your modules one by one. Make sure your store’s front office is working properly: try to create an account, place an order, to add a product, etc. Disable the maintenance mode in General settings &amp;gt; Maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update from the back office</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/update-from-the-back-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/update-from-the-back-office/</guid>
      <description>Update from the back officeThe Update Assistant module lets you update, backup and restore your PrestaShop store. Formerly known as “1-Click upgrade”, the technical name of this public module is “Autoupgrade”.&#xA;The module can be used in two main ways:&#xA;Through the module web user interface. Through the module Command-line (CLI). This documentation is meant to guide you through the use of these main assets.&#xA;Module downloadThe Update Assistant module can be downloaded from various sources:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update from the CLI</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/update-from-the-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/basics/keeping-up-to-date/update/update-from-the-cli/</guid>
      <description>Update from the Command-LineThe Update Assistant module is available through the Command-Line Interface (CLI). Its main advantage is its ability to integrate seamlessly with a CI/CD pipeline, enabling the automation of update, backup, and restore processes. Additionally, it can be executed manually through the CLI to bypass common configuration constraints on Apache or Nginx, such as php-cgi and php-fpm limitations (e.g., memory_limit, max_execution_time, etc.).&#xA;Introduction to the Update Assistant CLIThe CLI interface is a unified tool that provides a consistent interface for interacting with all Update Assistant module services.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
