<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frequently Asked Questions on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Frequently Asked Questions on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I need help</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/i-need-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/i-need-help/</guid>
      <description>I need help If you have questions or need help, please do not open a GitHub issue as we use GitHub issues only to discuss about bugs and new features for the PrestaShop project.
The very best place to start looking for an answer is:
 Here (the Developer documentation), if you are a developer The User&amp;rsquo;s guide if you are a user  If you are a developer and you think there is a missing item in the Developer documentation, consider creating an issue on the Documentation Repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image FAQ</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/image/</guid>
      <description>Image FAQ Q: Why can I not use more than 9 999 999 images?
A: The limitation of the .htaccess file prevents the use of more than 9 999 999 images because there is a limit of 9 back references ($1, $2, $3,&amp;hellip; $9) in mod_rewrite. The $10 $11 etc back references are being interpreted as just $1.
You can exceed this limitation by adding the needed rules in your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Project FAQ</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/open-source-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/open-source-project/</guid>
      <description>Open Source Project FAQ This section covers frequently asked questions about the Open Source Project.
Why is issue X still not fixed after so long? Not having an issue fixed immediately (or in a fixed timeframe) does not mean that it won&amp;rsquo;t be fixed, or that maintainers don&amp;rsquo;t care. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that the issue is NOT important either. It just means that other issues have been considered, for whatever reason, more important, so they were (or are being) tackled first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing FAQ</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/pricing/</guid>
      <description>Pricing FAQ  Refresh exchange rates  Refresh exchange rates Q: How can I make sure my currency exchange rates are regularly updated?
A: In PrestaShop, all currencies is associated with the exchange rate for Euro.
These exchange rates are updated every day by authorities in charge of these currencies.
The PrestaShop company gathers these rates and expose them through API endpoint https://api.prestashop.com/xml/currencies.xml (URL available in the code through constant _PS_CURRENCY_FEED_URL_).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product FAQ</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/product/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/product/</guid>
      <description>Product FAQ  Product cover  Product cover  Q: How can I override the cover image of my products?
A: By default, when a product is displayed in a list its cover image is used, it is configurable in the BackOffice and is set in product properties via the cover_image_id key. If you want to change this default behaviour you can use the actionGetProductPropertiesAfter in your module and change this key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shipping FAQ</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/shipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/shipping/</guid>
      <description>Shipping FAQ  Shipping information How do I add a service fee to an order?  Shipping information Q: Where and how should I read and write the following informations to be sure that my module is compatible with every shipping modules:
 Tracking number Carrier name Estimated delivery date Real delivery date  A: These details are stored at different places.
Carrier details Information related to a shipping (= delivery method) may be found / stored with the class Carrier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock FAQ</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/stock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/stock/</guid>
      <description>Stock FAQ  StockAvailable StockMovement  Q: Where exactly can I find the stock of a specified product?
A: All the stock information for every Product (and Combination) is stored in the StockAvailable entity/table. You will find duplicate values in Product and Combination object via their quantity fields, but they are deprecated fields that are only kept for backward compatibility and will be removed in future versions. The only true source of information for stock data is StockAvailable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade FAQ</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/faq/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Upgrade FAQ  After upgrading, I lost access to some Back-Office pages Upgrade fails with Error message JqXHR  Restore access to Back Office Page Q: After upgrading my PrestaShop to a new version, I lost access to some Back-Office pages. How can I fix it?
A: It is likely that some SQL configuration is not correct.
First, identify what is the slug of the Back Office pages. You can find them into the SQL table ps_authorization_role.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
