<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contribution guidelines on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contribution guidelines on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Writing a good commit message</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/writing-a-good-commit-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/writing-a-good-commit-message/</guid>
      <description>Writing a good commit messageCommit names should give an idea of the nature and context of the change that has been done. The more details, the better! The commit name should be as unique and recognizable as your commit itself. There are multitude of articles on the web regarding commit messages, here are two that you can find useful: How to Write a Git Commit Message and What makes a good commit message?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Describing Pull Requests</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/pull-requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/pull-requests/</guid>
      <description>The Pull Request formWhen you create a new Pull Request, you will be presented with a form that looks like this:&#xA;The first step is to write a summary of your pull request&amp;rsquo;s purpose in its GitHub title.&#xA;Writing a good titleA Pull Request title should be short, but precise enough to describe the changes it introduces and how they impact the software.&#xA;Please respect the following rules:&#xA;Be descriptive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported branches</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/supported-branches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/supported-branches/</guid>
      <description>Supported branchesMaintainers will only accept contributions for branches which are subject to new releases.&#xA;The development branch (develop) contains the development code for the next minor or major version, and is the natural destination for all contributions.&#xA;The patch version branch (e.g. 8.0.x) contains the code for the next patch release for a given version. This is where some bug fixes are destined, under specific conditions.&#xA;TL;DR When in doubt, target the develop branch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribution guidelines for modules</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/project-modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/project-modules/</guid>
      <description>Contribution guidelines for modulesThis document describes general guidelines for contributing to PrestaShop modules hosted on GitHub.&#xA;How to contributeContributors wishing to edit a module&amp;rsquo;s files should follow the following process:&#xA;Create your GitHub account, if you do not have one already.&#xA;Fork the project to your GitHub account.&#xA;Clone your fork to your local machine in the /modules directory of your PrestaShop installation.&#xA;Create a branch in your local clone of the module for your changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compatible licenses</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/compatible-licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/compatible-licenses/</guid>
      <description>Compatible licensesThe PrestaShop open source project is distributed under the OSL 3.0 license. All dependencies included and distributed with PrestaShop must be compatible with this license.&#xA;Software dependenciesBelow is a list of the known compatible licenses that can be accepted for software dependencies:&#xA;AFL Apache BSD CC-O EPL EUPL ISC MIT Unlicense ArtworkArtwork (including but not limited to: icons, pictures and fonts) is usually distributed with specific licenses. Below is a list of known compatible licenses that can be accepted for artwork:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI tests</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/ui-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/contribute/contribution-guidelines/ui-tests/</guid>
      <description>UI TestsUI tests have been built around PrestaShop in order to be able to verify whether new code changes do break an existing feature.&#xA;They work as follow&#xA;setup a docker instance with an installed shop running start a browser pilot the browser to perform actions on the web interface on the shop: click links, fill form and submit them, read &amp;lt;div&amp;gt; content&amp;hellip; These UI tests simulate the behavior of a real user.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
