<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advanced topics on PrestaShop Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advanced topics on PrestaShop Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installing PrestaShop with Docker &#43; PrestaShop Flashlight</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/prestashop-flashlight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/prestashop-flashlight/</guid>
      <description>Installing PrestaShop with Docker + PrestaShop FlashlightPrestaShop Flashlight was made to be able to start a PrestaShop instance within seconds.&#xA;It comes with default / demo content, Back Office access, and tools in the containers and in the Docker Compose manifest to run:&#xA;PhpMyAdmin (administration of MySQL over a web interface) Composer (dependency manager for PHP) php-cs-fixer (tool to apply code standards to your code) phpstan (PHP STatic ANalysis tool) phpunit (a PHP Testing Framework) timeline Setup environment : Install Docker : Clone Flashlight repository Install PrestaShop : Start Docker Compose stack Use / develop on PrestaShop : You are ready to go This installation method is not for production and should not be exposed to public traffic over the internet, please use it locally only, or at your own risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing PrestaShop from CLI</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/install-from-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/install-from-cli/</guid>
      <description>Installing PrestaShop from CLISince version 1.5.4, PrestaShop has a command-line installer.&#xA;This special installer makes it possible to install PrestaShop without the need to use a web browser: simply put the content of the zip archive on your web server or pull code from an official PrestaShop repository, and you can install PrestaShop through your command-line interface (CLI).&#xA;If deploying from sources (PrestaShop repository), you must first install Composer dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Apache Http</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/httpd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/httpd/</guid>
      <description>Configure Apache HttpdThe following file is provided as an example configuration for your Apache server. It may be incomplete, and remember you must adapt it for your own server&amp;rsquo;s needs!&#xA;In Apache 2.4, Order Allow,Deny has been replaced by Require all granted. We assume you are using Apache Http 2.4 or higher.&#xA;With mod_php/PHP-CGI&amp;lt;VirtualHost *:80&amp;gt; # or 443 for SSL support ServerName example.com DocumentRoot /path/to/prestashop # SSLEngine on # SSLCertificateFile /etc/apache2/ssl/example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Nginx</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/advanced/nginx/</guid>
      <description>Configure NginxThe following file is provided as an example configuration for your Nginx server. It may be incomplete, and remember you must adapt it for your own server&amp;rsquo;s needs!&#xA;Once you are comfortable with your setup make sure to review our guide on how to optimize your Nginx configuration to better suit your requirements.&#xA;server { # IPv4. listen 80; listen 443 ssl http2; # IPv6. # listen [::]:80; # listen [::]:443 ssl http2; # [EDIT] Your domain name(s) go here.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
