<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Translation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Translation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to translation</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to translationAt its core, translation consists in programmatically transforming a wording into its equivalent in a target language, using a translation dictionary. If the loaded dictionary is in Spanish, the output will be in Spanish.&#xA;VocabularyBefore you begin working with translations, you should get familiarized with the following concepts:&#xA;Wording (or &amp;ldquo;message&amp;rdquo;) An abstraction of a phrase that will be translated to any given language. It&amp;rsquo;s usually written as plain English, in order to make it easier to understand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translation Domains</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/translation-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/translation-domains/</guid>
      <description>Each string created for the PrestaShop project must be associated with a translation domain, to be later translated on Crowdin by the community of translators.&#xA;When a minor or major version of PrestaShop is released, all the new strings associated with this version are added to Crowdin to be translated.&#xA;Crowdin is a localization management platform on which a community of volunteer translators works on no less than 80 translation projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the Translator to translate wordings</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/using-the-translator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/using-the-translator/</guid>
      <description>Using the Translator to translate wordings This section provides an quick reference on how to use the Translator. For more information, read Symfony&amp;rsquo;s documentation on Using the Translator. PHP filesTo translate wordings in PHP files, you first need an instance of the Translator service (explained below). Then, you can use the trans() method to translate your wording:&#xA;&amp;lt;?php echo $translator-&amp;gt;trans(&amp;#39;This product is no longer available.&amp;#39;, [], &amp;#39;Shop.Notifications.Error&amp;#39;); The trans() method takes three arguments:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native module translation</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/native-module-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/native-module-translation/</guid>
      <description>Native module translation To find out the basics of module translation, read Module Translation. In PrestaShop lingo, &amp;ldquo;native modules&amp;rdquo; refers to all the modules that are bundled and distributed with the Core.&#xA;In difference with 3rd party modules, native modules&amp;rsquo; translation catalogues are distributed with the Core itself. Thanks to this, Native modules are translated using the New translation system since 1.7.0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips and tricks</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/translation-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/development/internationalization/translation/translation-tips/</guid>
      <description>Translation tips and tricks Adding new wordingsWordings for the Core and Native modules can only be translated if they are declared in PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s default translation catalogue. Therefore, whenever a new wording is added to the core or to a native module, it must be added to the default catalogue as well.&#xA;Normally you would have to manually add each wording the appropriate default catalogue files (located in the app/Resources/translations/default folder).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
