<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorials on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorials on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to use Bulk actions in Grid</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/work-with-bulk-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/work-with-bulk-actions/</guid>
      <description>How to use Bulk actions in Grid? In addition to displaying data tables, Grid component also comes with a lot of additional functionality. One of it is Bulk actions.
What is Bulk action? Bulk action is action (e.g. Delete, Change status &amp;amp; etc) that can be performed on multiple entries in table. This is a common task when using Grid (e.g. Delete multiple selected Suppliers with a single click).
How to add Bulk actions to Grid?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Grid Actions</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/work-with-grid-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/work-with-grid-actions/</guid>
      <description>How to use Grid actions In addition to displaying data tables, Grid component also comes with a lot of additional features. One is the Grid actions.
What is a Grid action? A Grid action is an action (e.g. Import, Export &amp;amp; Show SQL query) that is applicable to the entire Grid.
How to add actions to Grid? Let&amp;rsquo;s take an example from Customers grid definition. It has 5 (grid) actions already:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Row Actions</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/work-with-row-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/work-with-row-actions/</guid>
      <description>How to use Row actions In addition to displaying data tables, Grid component also comes with a lot of additional features. One is Row actions.
What is a Row action? A Row action is an action (e.g. Edit, View &amp;amp; Delete) that is applicable to a specific row in the Grid.
How to add row actions to Grid? Let&amp;rsquo;s take an example from Category grid definition. It has 3 (row) actions already:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to extend a Grid with Javascript extensions</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/extend-grid-with-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/extend-grid-with-javascript/</guid>
      <description>How to extend a grid with Javascript extensions Introduction Javascript grid extensions supplement grid behavior and enhance user experience. For example, most grids contains SortingExtension which provides sorting by columns functionality, BulkActionCheckboxExtension which enables interactive selection of bulk actions and so on. But the fact is that most of grids will not necessarily need all features, so by using extensions we encourage to easily add or remove grid feature while loading only necessary javascript code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to modify an existing Grid in a module</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/modify-grid-in-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/modify-grid-in-module/</guid>
      <description>How to modify an existing Grid in a module If you need to modify an existing Grid, like inverting two columns for instance, this is really easy to do it in a module thanks to the available hooks.
Business use case In this tutorial, we will try to improve the user experience of the Customers listing Grid (this page will be available in 1.7.6).
Thinking about it, we could improve the current grid to highlight business-driven information:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to customize the Grid templates</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/customize-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/customize-templates/</guid>
      <description>How to customize the Grid templates The Grid component is highly extensible from a structural and data point of view, but sometimes you need to customize how a grid, a row or a specific column is rendered.
For instance, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the Logs page of the PrestaShop Back Office. You can see that the &amp;ldquo;Employee&amp;rdquo; column have a specific rendering:
  Logs grid of PrestaShop with specific employee Column   In this tutorial, we will learn how to customize the rendering of every part of a Grid:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a custom Grid Action</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/create-custom-grid-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/create-custom-grid-action/</guid>
      <description>How to create a custom Grid Action Do you know how to do it? Please feel free to contribute to the docs! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a custom Column Type</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/create-custom-column-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/create-custom-column-type/</guid>
      <description>How to create a custom Column Type Do you know how to do it? Please feel free to contribute to the docs! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create an Empty state</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/create-empty-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/components/grid/tutorials/create-empty-state/</guid>
      <description>How to create an Empty state  Grid component allows developer to configure Empty state to make empty grid look more appealing for user.
Creating an Empty state By default, when Grid is empty user sees it as:
  Empty Suppliers grid   Unfortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s not very engaging, so let&amp;rsquo;s create Empty state for it! There are a few steps you have to follow:
 You have to create a template for it and put it in src/PrestaShopBundle/Resources/views/Admin/Common/Grid/Blocks/EmptyState directory, so Grid component can locate it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
