<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting started with theme development on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting started with theme development on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines and coding standards</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Guidelines and coding standards Compatibility PHP Code Your PHP code should be compatible with PHP compatibility chart
HTML / CSS / Javascript Your HTML/CSS/JS code should work with at least:
 Edge Firefox 45 Chrome 29.  Mobile-wise:
 iOS 8.4 Android Browser 4.4  Standards General Use spaces for indentation in every language (PHP, HTML, CSS, etc.):
4 spaces for PHP files, 2 spaces for all other file types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up your local environment</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/setting-up-your-local-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/setting-up-your-local-environment/</guid>
      <description>Setting up your local environment Now that you intend to building a theme for PrestaShop, you are better off keeping all your development work on your machine. The main advantage is that it makes it possible for you to entirely bypass the process of uploading your files on your online server in order to test your changes. Another advantage is that a local test environment enables you to test code without the risk of breaking your production store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tooling prerequisites for theme designers</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/tools-for-theme-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/tools-for-theme-designers/</guid>
      <description>Tooling prerequisites for theme designers The way 1.7 themes are created is significantly different from the way they were with PrestaShop 1.6. By taking the freedom to rewrite the way themes work according to the latest best-practices, we chose to also work with modern tools. These tools are widely accepted as best-of-breed in the current web development; hence, learning to use them will not only make you more productive in PrestaShop development, but more importantly in web development in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme organization</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/theme-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/theme-organization/</guid>
      <description>Theme organization Directory structure A PrestaShop theme is a set of files which you can edit in order to change the look of your online shop.
Here are a few important tidbits:
 All themes have their files located in the /themes folder, at the root of PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s folder. Each theme has its own sub-folder, in the main themes folder. Each theme is made of template files (.tpl), image files (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme.yml</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/theme-yml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/getting-started/theme-yml/</guid>
      <description>Theme.yml The theme&amp;rsquo;s theme.yml file defines all of the theme&amp;rsquo;s configuration and meta information, such as its version number, layouts, compatibility range, hook configuration, etc.
Theme description The theme&amp;rsquo;s name MUST match its directory name. For instance, if the theme is named &amp;ldquo;My Awesome Theme&amp;rdquo; and its &amp;lsquo;name&amp;rsquo; value is set to &amp;ldquo;my-awesome-theme&amp;rdquo;, then the folder MUST be /my-awesome-theme .
Users will be able to choose the layout for each page from the theme&amp;rsquo;s settings page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
