<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contribution guidelines on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contribution guidelines on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Writing a good commit message</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/writing-a-good-commit-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/writing-a-good-commit-message/</guid>
      <description>Writing a good commit message Commit names should give an idea of the nature and context of the change that has been done. The more details, the better! The commit name should be as unique and recognizable as your commit itself. There are multitude of articles on the web regarding commit messages, here are two that you can find useful: How to Write a Git Commit Message and What makes a good commit message?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Describing Pull Requests</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/pull-requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/pull-requests/</guid>
      <description>The Pull Request form When you create a new Pull Request, you will be presented with a form that looks like this:
The first step is to write a summary of your pull request&amp;rsquo;s purpose in its GitHub title.
Writing a good title A Pull Request title should be short, but precise enough to describe the changes it introduces and how they impact the software.
Please respect the following rules:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supported branches</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/supported-branches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/supported-branches/</guid>
      <description>Supported branches Maintainers should only accept contributions for branches which are subject to new releases.
Once a minor &amp;ldquo;dot-zero&amp;rdquo; version has been released, no new patch releases will be made for previous versions. This means that only the latest minor version patch branch is supported – with the exception of rare cases, like a security bug being found just before or after a minor release is published.
For example, the 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribution guidelines for modules</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/project-modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/project-modules/</guid>
      <description>Contribution guidelines for modules This document describes general guidelines for contributing to PrestaShop modules hosted on GitHub.
How to contribute Contributors wishing to edit a module&amp;rsquo;s files should follow the following process:
  Create your GitHub account, if you do not have one already.
  Fork the project to your GitHub account.
  Clone your fork to your local machine in the /modules directory of your PrestaShop installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compatible licenses</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/compatible-licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/contribution-guidelines/compatible-licenses/</guid>
      <description>Compatible licenses The PrestaShop open source project is distributed under the OSL 3.0 license. All dependencies included and distributed with PrestaShop must be compatible with this license.
Software dependencies Below is a list of the known compatible licenses that can accepted for software dependencies:
 AFL Apache BSD CC-O EPL EUPL ISC MIT Unlicense  Artwork Artwork (including but not limited to: icons, pictures and fonts) is usually distributed with specific licenses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
