<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Core changes on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Core changes on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Backward compatibility with PrestaShop 1.6</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.6/</guid>
      <description>Backward compatibility with PrestaShop 1.6 If you plan to develop a module for PrestaShop 1.7 then extending the compatibility with previous major versions of PrestaShop, it may require some changes before being ready for production.
Namespaces PrestaShop 1.6 does not fully support namespaces. They throw some issues when used in specific places.
 In the main class of your module, the keyword use [...]; will trigger syntax errors when PrestaShop will try to parse the file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make PrestaShop 1.6 modules compatible with 1.7</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.6-1.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.6-1.7/</guid>
      <description>Make PrestaShop 1.6 modules compatible with 1.7 Module front controllers There are several changes to templating in your module front controllers.
Getting a proper template for a page In order to display content properly in your ModuleFrontController files, you need to change the way you link to your template file in your initContent method:
- $this-&amp;gt;setTemplate(&amp;#39;views/templates/front/template.tpl&amp;#39;); + $this-&amp;gt;setTemplate(&amp;#39;module:yourmodule/views/templates/front/template.tpl&amp;#39;); Basic structure of a module front page template If you want your module to display an entire page with your own content, the basic structure of your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes in PrestaShop 1.7.5</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.7.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.7.5/</guid>
      <description>Notable changes in PrestaShop 1.7.5 LazyArrays Starting with PrestaShop 1.7.5, the business objects (Product, Order&amp;hellip;) available on the front-office are LazyArray instances. If your module relies on data available in the hook parameters or in the template, you may be concerned by this update.
They used to be arrays with all the data available. This change has been introduced to load the needed properties of an object only when requested, and globally improve the performance of the front-office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes in PrestaShop 1.7.6</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.7.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.7.6/</guid>
      <description>Notable changes in PrestaShop 1.7.6 CLDR The CLDR is a component responsible of displaying data such as the date &amp;amp; time, prices depending on a given language. It was reworked during several versions of PrestaShop 1.7, and will be enabled with 1.7.6. The previous one has been removed, and trying to use it will end to an exception.
A new variable is now available in the Context when going through a controller:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes in PrestaShop 1.7.7</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.7.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.7.7/</guid>
      <description>Notable changes in PrestaShop 1.7.7 PHP support PrestaShop 1.7.7 adds supports for PHP 7.3 and requires at least PHP 7.1.3. Older PHP versions are no longer supported.
Updated dependencies The following dependencies have been updated in order to provide support for PHP 7.3:
   Extension Old version New version     beberlei/doctrineextensions v1.1.9 v1.2.6   behat/transliterator v1.2.0 v1.3.0   composer/ca-bundle 1.1.4 1.2.6   composer/installers v1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes in PrestaShop 1.7.8</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.7.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/modules/core-updates/1.7.8/</guid>
      <description>Notable changes in PrestaShop 1.7.8 PHP support PrestaShop 1.7.8 adds supports for PHP 7.4.
Updated dependencies The following dependencies have been updated in order to provide support for PHP 7.4:
Production dependencies    Package name From To Compare     beberlei/doctrineextensions v1.2.6 v1.2.7 &amp;hellip;   composer/ca-bundle 1.2.6 1.2.8 &amp;hellip;   doctrine/annotations v1.8.0 1.10.4 &amp;hellip;   doctrine/cache 1.10.0 1.10.2 &amp;hellip;   doctrine/collections 1.6.4 1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
