<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The PrestaShop Webservice API on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/webservice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The PrestaShop Webservice API on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/webservice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/webservice/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/webservice/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started About CRUD &amp;amp; RESTThe PrestaShop web service uses the REST architecture in order to be available on as many platforms as possible, since the HTTP protocol and XML files are understood by most platforms, if not all.&#xA;CRUD is an acronym that stands for &amp;ldquo;Create, Read, Update, and Delete&amp;rdquo;. These are the four basic operations for managing data in an application.&#xA;REST defines roughly a style of software architecture, which promotes the use of HTTP methods when building web application, instead of custom methods or protocols such as SOAP or WSDL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/webservice/reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/webservice/reference/</guid>
      <description>Web service referenceAll webservice APIs are accessible through the /api/ gateway. For instance, http://example.com/api/carriers&#xA;Available HTTP methodsMost resources can be accessed in a REST manner, with the 5 main HTTP request methods: GET, POST, PUT, DELETE, HEAD. The only exceptions are:&#xA;Key GET POST PUT DELETE HEAD search ✅ ✅ stock_availables ✅ ✅ ✅ stock_movements ✅ ✅ stocks ✅ ✅ supply_order_details ✅ ✅ supply_order_histories ✅ ✅ supply_order_receipt_histories ✅ ✅ supply_order_states ✅ ✅ supply_orders ✅ ✅ warehouse_product_locations ✅ ✅ warehouses ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ All resources have two schemas that are accessible via a parameter:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheat sheet</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/webservice/cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/1.7/webservice/cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Cheat sheet for WebserviceAll these options can be added to your queries as query parameters (either GET or POST depending on the method used in your request).&#xA;Generic Options Key Value Description output_format XML, JSON Change the output format ps_method GET, POST, PUT, DELETE Override the HTTP method used for the request Resource options Key Value Result language 3 Only display localized fields in one language [3|5|...] Display localized fields for specified list of languages [2,5] Display localized fields for an interval of languages List options Key Value Description display display [field1,field2 …] Only display fields in brackets display full Display all fields filter filter[field] [1|5] OR operator: list of possible values filter[field] [1,10] Interval operator: define interval of possible values filter[field] [John] Literal value (not case sensitive) filter[field] [Jo]% Begin operator: fields begins with the value (not case sensitive) filter[field] %[hn] End operator: fields ends with the value (not case sensitive) filter[field] %[oh]% Contains operator: fields contains the value (not case sensitive) sort sort [field1_ASC,field2_DESC,field3_ASC] The sort value is composed of a field name and the expected order separated by a _ limit limit Number Limit the result to &amp;ldquo;Number&amp;rdquo; limit Starting index, Number Limit the result to &amp;ldquo;Number&amp;rdquo; from the &amp;ldquo;Index&amp;rdquo; Using the webservice in Multishop modeIn order to use web services when the Multishop feature is enabled, you need to add the id_shop parameter.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
