<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The PrestaShop Webservice API on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/webservice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The PrestaShop Webservice API on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/webservice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/webservice/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/webservice/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started About CRUD &amp;amp; REST The PrestaShop web service uses the REST architecture in order to be available on as many platforms as possible, since the HTTP protocol and XML files are understood by most platforms, if not all.
CRUD is an acronym that stands for &amp;ldquo;Create, Read, Update, and Delete&amp;rdquo;. These are the four basic operations for managing data in an application.
REST defines roughly a style of software architecture, which promotes the use of HTTP methods when building web application, instead of custom methods or protocols such as SOAP or WSDL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reference</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/webservice/reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/webservice/reference/</guid>
      <description>Web service reference All webservice APIs are accessible through the /api/ gateway. For instance, http://example.com/api/carriers
Available HTTP methods Most resources can be accessed in a REST manner, with the 5 main HTTP request methods: GET, POST, PUT, DELETE, HEAD. The only exceptions are:
   Key GET POST PUT DELETE HEAD     search ✅    ✅   stock_availables ✅ ✅   ✅   stock_movements ✅    ✅   stocks ✅    ✅   supply_order_details ✅    ✅   supply_order_histories ✅    ✅   supply_order_receipt_histories ✅    ✅   supply_order_states ✅    ✅   supply_orders ✅    ✅   warehouse_product_locations ✅    ✅   warehouses ✅ ✅ ✅  ✅    All resources have two schemas that are accessible via a parameter:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheat sheet</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/webservice/cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/webservice/cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Cheat sheet for Webservice All these options can be added to your queries as query parameters (either GET or POST depending on the method used in your request).
Generic Options    Key Value Description     output_format XML, JSON Change the output format   ps_method GET, POST, PUT, DELETE Override the HTTP method used for the request    Resource options    Key Value Result     language 3 Only display localized fields in one language    [3|5|.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
