<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>System requirements for PrestaShop 8</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>System requirements for PrestaShop 8PrestaShop needs the following server configuration in order to run:&#xA;Requirement Configuration Web server Apache Web Server 2.4 or any later version. (Although compatible, Apache Web Server 2.2 is not recommended since it reached its EOL in 2018). PHP We recommend PHP 8.1. See the compatibility chart below for more details. (Although compatible, PHP 7.2.5 to 8.0 are not recommended since they reached or will reach soon their end of support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing PrestaShop with Docker</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/environments/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/environments/docker/</guid>
      <description>Installing PrestaShop with DockerPrestaShop is available through Docker for testing/experimenting and developing modules or themes.&#xA;Docker is an open-source platform that enables developers to package applications and their dependencies into lightweight, portable containers. It provides an efficient and consistent way to build, ship, and run software across different environments.&#xA;Docker&amp;rsquo;s website PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s Docker Github repository PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s Docker Hub The easiest way to begin with PrestaShop on Docker is to run your stack with Docker Compose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing an AMP stack on MacOS</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/environments/macos-specific/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/environments/macos-specific/</guid>
      <description>Installing an AMP stack on MacOSPrestaShop is an Open-Source web application running on an *AMP stack (Apache - MySQL - PHP).&#xA;In order for PrestaShop to run locally on your MacOS computer, you need to install an *AMP stack.&#xA;Several options are available, such as:&#xA;XAMPP MAMP Brew + Apache + MySQL + PHP Use Docker to run PrestaShop on MacOSAnother good option when it comes to run PrestaShop on MacOS, is to use Docker: More informations on this dedicated page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing an AMP stack on Unix</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/environments/unix-specific/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/environments/unix-specific/</guid>
      <description>Installing an AMP stack on UnixPrestaShop is an Open-Source web application running on an *AMP stack (Apache - MySQL - PHP).&#xA;In order for PrestaShop to run locally on your computer, you need to install an *AMP stack.&#xA;Basically, you need to install:&#xA;Apache (or Nginx) MySQL PHP Please read this page or this one for guides to get started on installing Apache + MySQL + PHP on Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing an AMP stack on Windows</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/environments/windows-specific/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/basics/installation/environments/windows-specific/</guid>
      <description>Installing an AMP stack on WindowsPrestaShop is an Open-Source web application running on an *AMP stack (Apache - MySQL - PHP).&#xA;In order for PrestaShop to run locally on your Windows computer, you need to install an *AMP stack.&#xA;Several options are available, such as:&#xA;WAMP XAMPP EasyPHP MAMP Laragon Important notes when using Windows shell (CLI)Several examples in this documentation uses CLI (Command line interface), refered sometimes as terminal.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
