<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How to contribute on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/documentation/how/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How to contribute on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/documentation/how/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to edit a page on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/documentation/how/edit-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/documentation/how/edit-on-github/</guid>
      <description>How to edit a page on GitHub Editing a page on GitHub is the most straight-forward way of contributing content to PrestaShop DevDocs.
 The good: you don&amp;rsquo;t need to have anything installed. The bad: even if GitHub provides a preview of your markdown code, you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to see exactly how it will look like on the site (for instance, shortcodes aren&amp;rsquo;t interpreted by the GitHub preview).  For this tutorial, you will need a GitHub account (free).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to edit a page on your computer</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/documentation/how/edit-on-your-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/documentation/how/edit-on-your-computer/</guid>
      <description>How to edit a page on your computer using Git Running a local copy of DevDocs on your computer is the best way to work on this project. Even though it requires a little extra work to set up, you will gain the ability to preview your changes almost instantly, as well as being able to introduce more than one change at a time.
Prerequisites To run a local DevDocs install on your system, you will need:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Markdown</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/documentation/how/writing-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/contribute/documentation/how/writing-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Writing Markdown This site was created using the wonderful Hugo static site generator, but the content itself is written using Markdown.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to know anything about Hugo or the Go language to write documentation. The Markdown syntax is basically plain text with some simple added syntax for styling.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know Markdown yet, have a look at this quick Markdown guide from GitHub.
Extended features: Shortcodes Hugo uses special short codes for many things.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
