<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Core changes on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/modules/core-updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Core changes on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/modules/core-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Changes in PrestaShop 8.0</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/modules/core-updates/8.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/modules/core-updates/8.0/</guid>
      <description>Notable changes in PrestaShop 8.0 PHP supportPrestaShop 8.0 adds supports for PHP 8.0 and PHP 8.1 and requires at least PHP 7.2.5.&#xA;Notable changes Javascript files for migrated pages in the Back Office now are written in TypeScript (related change: #24791). Support for legacy translation dictionaries (eg: en.php, fr.php&amp;hellip;, deprecated in 1.7), has been removed from Core controllers. Only modules can still use this system now. All modules present in the modules directory during the installation process will be installed by default (except in the web-based installation where you can unselect some of them).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes in PrestaShop 8.1</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/modules/core-updates/8.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/modules/core-updates/8.1/</guid>
      <description>Notable changes in PrestaShop 8.1 PHP supportPrestaShop 8.1 has the same PHP requirement as Prestashop 8.0.&#xA;PrestaShop 8.0 added support for PHP 8.0 and PHP 8.1 and required at least PHP 7.2.5.&#xA;New product pageThe new Product page in Back Office has been introduced. Discover how to extend it with modules in this chapter.&#xA;Notable changes Introduction of _raw parameter on translations to avoid html escaping in translator. PR#30415 Changed location of Smarty caching type configuration from database to config/defines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New password policy based on zxcvbn</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/modules/core-updates/new-password-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop-project.org/8/modules/core-updates/new-password-policy/</guid>
      <description>New password policy introduced in 8.0.xA new password policy was introduced in 8.0.x for Customers and Employees passwords.&#xA;This password policy is based on Zxcvbn.&#xA;Zxcvbn is a password strength estimation library that is designed to help developers create secure password policies for their applications. It was developed by DropBox and is available as an open-source library.&#xA;It estimates the strength of a password by analyzing various factors such as its length, the use of special characters, and the presence of common words or patterns.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
