<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Templates on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Templates on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Templates &amp; layouts</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/templates-layouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/templates-layouts/</guid>
      <description>Templates &amp;amp; layouts PrestaShop template file are based on the Smarty 3 template engine.
All template files must be stored in the theme&amp;rsquo;s templates/ subfolder. For instance, the default theme has its template files in the following folder: /themes/classic/templates.
Directory structure Templates are then split between various subfolders.
 /_partials/ Code shared accross the whole site like header, footer or notifications. /catalog/ Product page, product/brand/supplier listing, search result and such. /checkout/ Cart, delivery options, payement options, order confirmations and such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/head/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/head/</guid>
      <description>Head The head part is very important in term of SEO and performances.
Have look at Classic&amp;rsquo;s head part to see real life examples.
Assets PrestaShop 1.7 changed the way asset works and it means the way to it&amp;rsquo;s added inside the &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; tag of your page changed a bit too.
There are 2 importants files to use:
 _partials/stylesheets.tpl _partials/javascript.tpl  These 2 files are used to take full advantage of the new features of 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notifications</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/notifications/</guid>
      <description>Notifications Throughout the whole front office, the customer can receive notification messages from PrestaShop, to inform about successes or errors for instance. Your theme can also send notifications when certain events occur.
The notification messages are not hard-coded in the template files, but are sent from the controller, so that you have consistency in case you update/change your theme. Thus, this way there is a better chance that all notification messages are already translated into your language!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listing pages</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/listing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/reference/templates/listing/</guid>
      <description>Listing pages Your catalog is mostly 2 things: a list of products and a detailed product page.
This section covers the listing pages, which includes: category, search result, products per brand, best seller list, new product list and so on.
In order to reduce code duplication, the only necessary template is the file catalog/listing/product-list.tpl.
Extending product-list template We already covered how PrestaShop chooses the right template to use so we know that the category template extends the product-list template.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
